Guide to the Social Service Employees Union Photographs PHOTOS 014
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Color Photographs, 1991-2005
  - Subseries A: Snapshots
    - Bargaining: Collective (Corresponding negatives for these images may be found in Series IV: Negatives, Subseries B: Color negatives), Dec 2005 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Bargaining: Collective Social Service and Related Titles (SSRT), 2005 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Black History Month Celebration (Honoring Gloria Richardson-Dandridge), 1995 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Black History Month Celebration, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Black History Month Celebration, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Black History Month Celebration, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Black History Month Celebration, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Caribbean Heritage, undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Caribbean Heritage (Corresponding negatives for these images, on Advantix cassette #s 204-495 and 975-273, may be found in Series IV: Negatives, Subseries B: Color), 2001 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Caribbean Heritage (Corresponding negatives for these images may be found in Series IV: Negatives, Subseries B: Color negatives), 2002 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Christmas Celebrations at Administration for Children's Services (ACS) Locations, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Christmas Celebrations at ACS Locations, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - City Council Hearing on Department of Homeless Services (DHS) (Corresponding negatives for these images may be found in Series IV: Negatives, Subseries B: Color negatives), Dec 1998 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Civil Service Month, Oct 30, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Coalition of Jewish Organizations' Breakfast, Oct 2002 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Conference: AFL-CIO Legislative endorses Hillary Clinton for Senator, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Conference: AFL-CIO, 371 demonstrates in support of striking hotel workers, Chicago, Illinois, Jun 2003 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Conference: American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Washington, DC, Mar 19, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Conference: AFSCME Women's, Boston, Massachusetts, Oct 2003 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Conference: Labor Council for Latin American Advancement (LCLAA), Chicago, Illinois (Corresponding negatives for these images, on Advantix cassette #s 534-169 and 534-341, may be found in Series IV: Negatives, Subseries B: Color.), Aug 2000 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Conference: Somos el Futuro, Albany, New York, Apr 2002 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Convention: AFL-CIO, includes demonstration in support of striking hotel workers, Los Angeles, California, [1999?] (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Convention: AFSCME, includes demonstration to support DC 33, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (Corresponding negatives for these images, including Advantix cassette #277-023, may be found in Series IV: Negatives, Subseries B: Color.), Jun 2000 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Convention: AFSCME, includes demonstration for contract at Golden Nugget Casino, Las Vegas, Nevada, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Convention: AFSCME, United States Senator John Kerry, keynote speaker, Anaheim, California, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Dedication Ceremony for Lower Eastside Hospital, Jun 2002 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Delegate Training, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Delegate Training, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Delegate Training, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Delegate Training, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Demonstration: Against Iraq War, Spring 2002 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Demonstration: Against Iraq War, Washington, DC, Summer 2005 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Demonstration: Against Layoffs, Sponsored by District Council (DC) 37, Sep 2002 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Demonstration: Against State Budget Cuts, Albany, Mar 1991 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Demonstration: Air Quality near Ground Zero (Corresponding negatives for these images may be found in Series IV: Negatives, Subseries B: Color, on Advantix cassette # 194-356.), Oct 12, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Demonstration: DC 37 members at City Hall Park for new contract, Oct 29, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Demonstration: For a new contract, City Hall, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Demonstration: "One Member-One Vote", Fall 2005 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Demonstration: Protesting shooting death of Amadu Dialo, New York City (Corresponding negatives for these images may be found in Series IV: Negatives, Subseries B: Color.), Feb 2000 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Demonstration: Protesting shooting death of Amadu Dialo, Washington, DC (Corresponding negatives for these images may be found in Series IV: Negatives, Subseries B: Color.), Mar 2, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Demonstration: Social Service Commission (SSC) in City Hall Park, Jun 20, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Demonstration: Support the Transit Workers' Union (TWU), Dec 2002 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Demonstration: 371 at City Hall Park against contracting out, Jun 1994 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Demonstration: 371 in support of Local 375 "no contracting out", undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Demonstration: 371 in support of new contract for DC 1707, Oct 2003 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Demonstration: 371 supporting Local 420 against hospital closings, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Demonstration: 371 supporting Local 420 "Save the Hospitals" campaign, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Demonstration: 371 supports Local 1407's new contract, Nov 2003-Dec 2003 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Demonstration: 371 supports EMS workers new contract, Dec 2005 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Demonstration: 371 supports TWU, Dec 2003 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Demonstration: Vieques, Puerto Rico (Corresponding negatives for these images may be found in Series IV: Negatives, Subseries B: Color negatives), [2001?] (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - DC 37's Civil Service Committee Award to Victor Gotbaum, Nov 2003 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Endorsement of Steve Di Brenza for Public Advocate, Aug 2001 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Ensley, Charles (President) at various events, 1997-2000, undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Ensley meets with presidential candidates at American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) headquarters, Sep 2003 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Epstein, Dorothy: made honorary member of 371, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Fasanella, Ralph with Pete Seeger, May 1995 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Fishgold, Martin (Unionist Editor) presents awards, Oct 2003 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Gray, Shirley, undated (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Grievance Staff Delegates' Training, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Halloween party for children at Administration for Children's Services (ACS), 2003 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Hope, Bertha (Corresponding negatives for these images may be found in Series IV: Negatives, Subseries B: Color, on Advantix cassette #637-589.), undated (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Investigation of sanitary and health problems at Coney Island Hospital Annex, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Jewish Heritage, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Jewish Heritage, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Jewish Heritage, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Jewish Heritage, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Jewish Heritage, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Jorge, Julia with Shirley Aldebol, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Labor Day, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Labor Day Corresponding negatives for these images may be found in Series IV: Negatives, Subseries B: Color, on Advantix cassette #196-358.), 2002 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Labor Day (Corresponding negatives for these images may be found in Series IV: Negatives, Subseries B: Color.), 2003 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Labor Workshop, Raleigh, North Carolina (Corresponding negatives for these images may be found in Series IV: Negatives, Subseries B: Color.), Apr 14, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Latino Heritage, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Latino Heritage, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Martin Luther King Day Celebration, Atlanta, Georgia, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Martin Luther King Day Celebration, Atlanta, Georgia, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Martin Luther King Day Celebration, Greensboro, North Carolina, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Martin Luther King Day Celebration, Miami, Florida, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Martin Luther King Day Celebration, Jackson, Mississippi "Demonstration for Jobs and Justice", 2003 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - May Day Participants, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Mayoral candidate Mark Green endorsement, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Meeting: Delegate Assembly (presidential nominations), Mar 2005 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Meeting: Retirees with Public Advocate Betsy Gotbaum, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Meeting: 371 Political Action Committee (PAC), 2004 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Meeting: Women's Committee, undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Meeting: Women's Committee (Guest Dr. J. Biggers), 2002 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Meeting: Women's Committee at AFSCME Conference, Mar 26, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - New Orleans' Trip (Corresponding negatives for these images may be found in Series IV: Negatives, Subseries B: Color.), 1999 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Nicelli (Corresponding negatives for these images, on Advantix cassette # 015-028, may be found in Series IV: Negatives, Subseries B: Color), 2001 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Orientation of new caseworkers, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Phone Bank: Vice President Wana Ulyses, and PAC during election, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Retiree Association Honors Charles Ensley, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Retirement Lunch, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Savino, Diane (Vice-President):Testifies before City Council; addressing Working Families Party, Mar 25, 2003, undated (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Social Work Month Celebration, Mar 31, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Social Work Month Celebration, Mar 2003 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Social Work Month Celebration, Mar 2005 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Strong, Michael: Union member starring in play about the homeless, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - 37th Anniversary of "March on Washington", 2000 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - 371 members provide counseling services to 9/11 victims, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Voter registration drive in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Working Families Party [meeting] in Albany, New York, [2000?] (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - World Peace March, May 21, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Subseries B: Panorama size
    - Conference: Labor Council for Latin American Advancement (LCLAA), Chicago, Illinois (Corresponding negatives for these images, on Advantix cassette #s 534-169 and 534-341, may be found in Series IV: Negatives, Subseries B: Color), Aug 2000 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Jewish Heritage, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Jewish Heritage, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Labor Day, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Series IV: Negatives, 1975-2002
  - Subseries A: Black and White
    - Correspond to contact sheets # 1106-1155, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Correspond to contact sheets # 1155-1217, 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Correspond to contact sheets # 1218-1266, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Correspond to contact sheets # 1266-1312, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Correspond to contact sheets # 1313-1358, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Correspond to contact sheets # 1358-1404, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Correspond to contact sheets # 1404-1454, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Correspond to contact sheets # 1455-1499C, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Correspond to contact sheets # 1499C-1591, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Correspond to contact sheets: Charles Ensley, Aug 1982 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Correspond to contact sheets, Mid 1990s (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Correspond to contact sheets, 1992-1996 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Correspond to contact sheets, 1996-2002 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Do not have corresponding contact sheets, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Do not have corresponding contact sheets, Mid 1990s (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Subseries B: Color
    - Correspond to miscellaneous photographs, 1998-2005 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Do not have matching prints, Mid 1990s (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Advantix Cassette # 015-028, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Advantix Cassette # 194-356, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Advantix Cassette # 196-358, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Advantix Cassette # 204-495, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Advantix Cassette # 277-023, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Advantix Cassette # 534-169, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Advantix Cassette # 534-341, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Advantix Cassette # 538-510, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Advantix Cassette # 637-589, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Advantix Cassette # 747-361, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Advantix Cassette # 766-424, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Advantix Cassette # 796-307, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Advantix Cassette # 975-273, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Series V: Compact Discs, 1997-2002
  - African-American Parade [two discs], 2002 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - African-American Parade, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 2002 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - AFSCME, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - AFSCME, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - AFSCME, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - AFSCME, undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - AFSCME, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - BX Club B/W, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Caribbean [Heritage], 2002 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Celebration of the Opening of the Union's Archives at NYU [power point presentation], Apr 25, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Faye's Award and John Hudson's Retirement, May 2002 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Faye's Civil Service Award and Italian Heritage, Oct 17, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Italian Heritage, Oct 19, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Italian Heritage, Oct 19, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Jewish Heritage, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Joe's Award, undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Latino Heritage, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Latino Heritage, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Latino Heritage, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Local 1457 and McCall, undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - NAACP and Photo Class B/W, undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - San Francisco, Sep 4, 2002-Sep 8, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - San Francisco, Sep 4, 2002-Sep 8, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - San Francisco, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - San Francisco, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - San Francisco, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - San Francisco, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Suella Gallop], 2002 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Suella, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Suella/Bargaining, Nov 7, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Suella with Truitt's photo, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Velma/Delegate Assembly, Sep 2002 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Villa Roma, undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Washington D.C. Legislative Conference, Mar 16, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Wynette, undated (Box 17, Folder 36)
- Series VI: Unprocessed, 1985-2007, 1985-2007 (bulk 1980s-1990s); 1985-1999; 9 Linear Feet Eight records boxes; one large flat box.
  - Box 18
  - Box 19
  - Box 20
  - Box 21
  - Box 22
  - Box 23
  - Box 24
  - Box 25
  - Box 26